Congratulations.恭喜你
Publishing an app to Google  在 Google Play 上发布应用是非常独特和强大的
Play is a unique and powerful
opportunity. 机会
So from designing and developing 从设计和开发应用 到为发布
an app to preparing it
for the Play Store, you've 在 Play 商店中做准备 你完成并学到了很多
done and learned a lot.
Remember that users 记住 用户安装你的应用
install your app
because they believe 是因为他们相信你的产品
in your product,
and their continued 而让他们继续在使用中获得乐趣
enjoyment of using your app
is your benchmark for success.便是你取得成功的基准
So with thousands of new 每周发布的新应用有成千上万个
apps published every week,
there are active 你可以主动采取一些措施
steps that you can
do to ensure yours gets the 来确保获得最大的可见性和最高的
most visibility and the highest
ratings possible. 得分
Learn from other 你可以从其他开发人员那里学习
developers on how
to continue optimizing 如何继续优化你的应用
your app for success
and be able to 并从中实现利润
monetize your app,
as well as how to continue 以及如何继续为用户
providing the best
experience for your users.提供最佳的体验
Now Google provides a plethora    Google 提供了大量资源 来帮助开发人员
of resources for developers
to continue 继续改进他们的应用
improving their apps.
Learn how to choose the 了解如何选择正确的营利模式
correct monetization
model to how to sell goods 以及如何使用 Android Play 销售商品与服务
and services with Android Play.
Google also provides     Google 还提供了一个强大的分析工具
a powerful analytics
tool called Firebase Analytics. 叫作 Firebase Analytics
It's a free tool that gives  这是一款免费工具 可以让你作为开发人员
you as the developer insights
into how users are using  了解用户使用你的应用和与之交互的方式
and engaging with your app
so that you can continue making 以持续在应用营销和改进方面
informed decisions about how
to market and improve 做出明智的决定
your application.
Now something that I 我经常会听到很多其他开发人员
always find inspiring
is hearing the stories of how 通过 Android 和 Google Play 商店取得成功的故事
many other developers have
found success with 这让我备受鼓舞
Android and Google Play.
Check out their  你可以查看这些开发人员的故事
developer stories
and hear strategies 聆听他们增加安装量的策略
to increase installs,
improve user experiences 以及如何通过材料设计提高用户体验
with material design,
and turn your personal passion 进而将你的个人爱好转变为成功的商业机会
into a successful business.
And again, congratulations. 再次祝贺你
You've accomplished a lot to 到这一步你完成了很多
get to this state, all the way
from developing, to testing, to 从开发到测试 到设置应用
setting your app for success,
to now engaging with your users.再到与用户交互
Now give yourself a 现在你可以肯定地拍拍自己的肩膀
big pat on the back
and go out and celebrate the 出去与朋友庆祝完成的这项重大的工作
hard work that you've done.
Now that your app 现在你的应用已经发布
is out in the world,
take advantage of all the 那么就充分利用可用的所有工具与资源
tools and resources available
and continue making it 持续打造令人兴奋的体验吧
an amazing experience.